{
  "ieltsplustree-test1-reading": [
    {
      "part": 1,
      "test_name": "Reducing Electricity Consumption on the Isle of Eigg",
      "text": "",
      "section": "Reading",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question_number": 1,
          "question_text": "Approximately how many people live on Eigg?",
          "question_type": "Short Answer",
          "answer": "About a hundred"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 2,
          "question_text": "What proportion of a UK household’s electricity consumption does an Eigg household consume?",
          "question_type": "Short Answer",
          "answer": "50 percent"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 3,
          "question_text": "Apart from wind and sun, where does most of Eigg’s electricity come from?",
          "question_type": "Short Answer",
          "answer": "Water"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 4,
          "question_text": "What device measures the amount of electricity Eigg’s households are using?",
          "question_type": "Short Answer",
          "answer": "Energy monitors"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 5,
          "question_text": "When renewable energy supplies are insufficient, what backs them up?",
          "question_type": "Short Answer",
          "answer": "Diesel generators"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 6,
          "question_text": "What has EHT provided free of charge in all the houses it owns?",
          "question_type": "Short Answer",
          "answer": "Insulation"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 7,
          "question_text": "Which gardening aid did some Eigg inhabitants claim grants for?",
          "question_type": "Short Answer",
          "answer": "Greenhouses"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 8,
          "question_text": "Electricity was available for the first time on Eigg when a new grid was switched on.",
          "question_type": "True/False/Not Given",
          "answer": "False"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 9,
          "question_text": "Eigg’s carbon emissions are now much lower than before.",
          "question_type": "True/False/Not Given",
          "answer": "True"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 10,
          "question_text": "Wood will soon be the main source of heating on Eigg.",
          "question_type": "True/False/Not Given",
          "answer": "True"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 11,
          "question_text": "Eigg is quieter as a result of having a new electricity supply.",
          "question_type": "True/False/Not Given",
          "answer": "Not Given"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 12,
          "question_text": "Well-off households pay higher prices for the use of extra electricity.",
          "question_type": "True/False/Not Given",
          "answer": "False"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 13,
          "question_text": "The new electricity grid has created additional employment opportunities on Eigg.",
          "question_type": "True/False/Not Given",
          "answer": "True"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "part": 2,
      "test_name": "Change in Business Organisations",
      "text": "",
      "section": "Reading",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question_number": 14,
          "question_text": "Some specific predictions about businesses and working practices.",
          "question_type": "Paragraph Matching",
          "answer": "F"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 15,
          "question_text": "Reference to the way company employees were usually managed.",
          "question_type": "Paragraph Matching",
          "answer": "B"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 16,
          "question_text": "A warning for business leaders.",
          "question_type": "Paragraph Matching",
          "answer": "G"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 17,
          "question_text": "The description of an era notable for the relative absence of change.",
          "question_type": "Paragraph Matching",
          "answer": "A"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 18,
          "question_text": "A reason why customer satisfaction was not a high priority.",
          "question_type": "Paragraph Matching",
          "answer": "C"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 19,
          "question_text": "A surplus of goods.",
          "question_type": "Characteristic Matching",
          "answer": "B"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 20,
          "question_text": "An emphasis on production quantity.",
          "question_type": "Characteristic Matching",
          "answer": "B"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 21,
          "question_text": "The proximity of consumers to workplaces.",
          "question_type": "Characteristic Matching",
          "answer": "A"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 22,
          "question_text": "A focus on the quality of goods.",
          "question_type": "Characteristic Matching",
          "answer": "C"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 23,
          "question_text": "New products and new ways of working.",
          "question_type": "Characteristic Matching",
          "answer": "C"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 24,
          "question_text": "What proportion of employees will be temporary workers by 2020?",
          "question_type": "Summary Completion",
          "answer": "20-25 percent"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 25,
          "question_text": "Where will half of employees work by 2020?",
          "question_type": "Summary Completion",
          "answer": "Home"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 26,
          "question_text": "What do business leaders need to understand to manage organisational change?",
          "question_type": "Summary Completion",
          "answer": "Forces"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "part": 3,
      "test_name": "Future of Work",
      "text": "",
      "section": "Reading",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question_number": 27,
          "question_text": "Experiments by Bernard Agranoff described in Reading Passage 3 involved",
          "question_type": "multiple_choice",
          "options": {
            "A": "injecting goldfish at different stages of the experiments.",
            "B": "training goldfish to do different types of task.",
            "C": "using different types of treatment on goldfish.",
            "D": "comparing the performance of different goldfish on certain tasks."
          }
        },
        {
          "question_number": 28,
          "question_text": "Most findings from recent studies suggest that",
          "question_type": "multiple_choice",
          "options": {
            "A": "drug treatments do not normally affect short-term memories.",
            "B": "long-term memories build upon short-term memories.",
            "C": "short and long-term memories are formed by separate processes.",
            "D": "ECT treatment affects both short and long-term memories."
          }
        },
        {
          "question_number": 29,
          "question_text": "In the fifth paragraph, what does the writer want to show by the example of staircases?",
          "question_type": "multiple_choice",
          "options": {
            "A": "Prompt memory formation underlies the performance of everyday tasks.",
            "B": "Routine tasks can be carried out unconsciously.",
            "C": "Physical accidents can impair the function of memory.",
            "D": "Complex information such as regulations cannot be retained by the memory."
          }
        },
        {
          "question_number": 30,
          "question_text": "Observations about memory by Kami and Sagi",
          "question_type": "multiple_choice",
          "options": {
            "A": "cast doubt on existing hypotheses.",
            "B": "related only to short-term memory.",
            "C": "were based on tasks involving hearing.",
            "D": "confirmed other experimental findings."
          }
        },
        {
          "question_number": 31,
          "question_text": "What did the experiment by Shadmehr and Holcomb show?",
          "question_type": "multiple_choice",
          "options": {
            "A": "Different areas of the brain were activated by different tasks.",
            "B": "Activity in the brain gradually moved from one area to other areas.",
            "C": "Subjects continued to get better at a task after training had finished.",
            "D": "Treatment given to subjects improved their performance on a task."
          }
        },
        {
          "question_number": 32,
          "question_text": "The training which Kami and Sagi’s subjects were given was repeated over several days.",
          "question_type": "yes_no_not_given"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 33,
          "question_text": "The rats in Weinberger’s studies learned to associate a certain sound with a specific experience.",
          "question_type": "yes_no_not_given"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 34,
          "question_text": "The results of Weinberger’s studies indicated that the strength of the rats’ learned associations increases with time.",
          "question_type": "yes_no_not_given"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 35,
          "question_text": "It is easy to see the evolutionary advantage of the way lasting memories in humans are created.",
          "question_type": "yes_no_not_given"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 36,
          "question_text": "Long-term memories in humans are more stable than in many other species.",
          "question_type": "yes_no_not_given"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 37,
          "question_text": "Laboratory experiments usually involve teaching subjects to do something ________, and treating them with mild electric shocks or drugs.",
          "options": {
            "A": "early",
            "B": "easy",
            "C": "large",
            "D": "late",
            "E": "lengthy",
            "F": "new",
            "G": "recently",
            "H": "small",
            "I": "quick"
          },
          "question_type": "fill_in_the_blank"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 38,
          "question_text": "The results are generally consistent: they show that lasting memories are the result of a _______ and complex biological process.",
          "options": {
            "A": "early",
            "B": "easy",
            "C": "large",
            "D": "late",
            "E": "lengthy",
            "F": "new",
            "G": "recently",
            "H": "small",
            "I": "quick"
          },
          "question_type": "fill_in_the_blank"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 39,
          "question_text": "The fact that humans share this trait with other species, including animals with _______ brains, suggests that it developed ______ in our evolutionary history.",
          "options": {
            "A": "early",
            "B": "easy",
            "C": "large",
            "D": "late",
            "E": "lengthy",
            "F": "new",
            "G": "recently",
            "H": "small",
            "I": "quick"
          },
          "question_type": "fill_in_the_blank"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}